(Bernadette:)and one day you wake up
and you're pregnant.
(Bernadette:)And it doesn't matter that your
career's going great right now
(Bernadette:)and that you and your husband
never even got to go anywhere
taped to a dog!
(Raj:)I skipped spin class for this.
(Howard:)Why is it taking him so long
(Howard:)to get a drink out
of a vending machine?
(Leonard:)Oh, it's complicated.
(Leonard:)He finds pushing
that little door
(Leonard:)and reaching up into the machine
uncomfortably intimate.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I am ready to work.
To quote The Martian, "Let's
science the feces out of this!"
That's The Martian the book
and The Martian the movie,
not Marvin the Martian.
(Sheldon:)Although to quote
Marvin the Martian,
"I claim this planet
in the name of Mars."
(Leonard:)Are you okay?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm fantastic,
never been better.
(Sheldon:)I had my first energy drink
(Sheldon:)and I feel great.
(Sheldon:)Hey, you guys want to wrestle?
(Sheldon:)We can do arm,
thumb, mud, sumo.
(Sheldon:)Nah, we're not fat enough,
or wearing diapers.
(Howard:)You wanted him awake.